

Qianqian Wang

UI/UX Designer

🛡 San Francisco, USA

Profile

I have always been a person fascinated with visual design. In past few years, I have focused on incorporating the latest design trends, which have expanded my skillset. I take great pride in my ability to think outside the box, and my attention to details has always generated successful results of an improved user experience.

Experience

UI/UX Designer @ KidzJet

10/2015 - 12/2015

- Developed pixel-perfect wireframe and mock-ups for KidzJet web-based dashboard and mobile app.
- Participated in all phases of the product development lifecycle from ideation and definition, to interface design, user research and testing.
- Worked directly with the product team and CEO to provide style guides and navigational flows; ensuring that engineers adhere to style specifications.

UI Designer @ Hubtag Inc.

06/2015 - 10/2015

- Designed pixel-perfect mockups for Hubtag live streaming software dashboard, and enhancing users experience by providing new responsive layout for mobile devices.
- Redesigned Hubtag official landing page website, by creating wireframes and hi-fi mockups for new layouts.
- Conducted user research, then analyzed and translated feedback into effective and innovative user experience.

UX Designer and Team Leader @ UW Capstone Tagether 12/2014 - 06/2015

- Led in the design for the user interfaces for Tagether, a cloud based Chrome extension web application.
- Designed the Capstone presentation poster and created promotion video for introducing the application at Chrome Web Store.

Research Librarian @ Seattle Public Library

11/2014 - 07/2015

Provided research support by gathering data and compiling information for management purposes and objectives.

Education

University of Washinton, Information School

09/2013 - 06/2015

Master of Library and Information Science

Shanghai University, Department of Library and Archives

08/2009 - 06/2013

Bachelor of Arts in Library and Archives

Contacts

Emeryville, CA 94607 (206)953-0326 qianq222@uw.edu www.qianqianwang.design

I use

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Sketch

Adobe Muse

Adobe After Effect

HTML / CSS

Microsoft Office

XML

I excel at

Sketching

Wireframing

User Research

User Interface Design

Concept Development

I am

Imaginative

Creative

Collaborative

I speak

Mandarin / Cantonese

English

Korean